[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series
are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
I’ll do everything to find Key.
Key.
Thank you for saving me.
Key, honey.
I was the one who made her condition worse.
It was my fault.
You’re the best dad to me.
Are we really going to sleep over here?
You can’t sleep?
Yes.
Are you afraid?
I’m afraid that if I fall asleep,
I will have a nightmare about my mom.
I don’t want to see it again.
If you don’t want to have the nightmare again,
why don’t we face it together?
Key.
It’s okay.
It’s alright.
You are okay now.
Everything was just the past.
How are you feeling?
Did you get a good sleep last night?
Mom.
I miss you.
I’m right here.
Do you know…
how incredible you are?
My daughter is the best.
I love you, Mom.
I love you, too.
So Key,
you don’t need to be sad,
feel hurt,
or feel guilty anymore.
The love you gave me made me very happy.
Key, promise me.
You will go on living a happy life.
Can you do that?
I promise.
I will be happy.
You are smiling.
Did you have a good dream?
Yes.
I had a good dream.
I dreamt of my mom.
I promised her that I would be happy.
That’s great.
You are my happiness.
What did the doctor say?
We talked a lot.
I haven’t seen a psychiatrist for a while.
So I needed to update her about my condition.
She said I made the right decision to receive counselling again.
In the meantime,
I will receive counselling
and take the prescribed medication.
Did she give you other recommendations?
Is there anything that can help you heal?
She said that having someone I love,
someone who understands me by my side,
would be a big help.
I already have them.
I have you and everyone in my family.
Thank you, Chan, for keeping me company today.
Company?
I’m your girlfriend.
Okay.
Thank you for being my girlfriend.
I will be by your side and stick to you every day.
Then I will stick to you
like I'm attached to you at the hip.
Before we go home, we should go shopping for Simba’s stuff.
Sure.
What are you going to buy for him?
I don’t know.
I just want to buy him something.
Don’t you want to buy anything for this one?
For this one,
I’ll take care of her for the rest of my life.
Come on.
Let’s go shopping.
Yeah.
Where are you going?
I’m going to Paris.
I have a shooting there.
Didn’t you just come back from Milan?
Are you leaving again?
When an opportunity comes my way, I have to take it, right?
How long will you be away?
Around two weeks.
Two weeks?
Yes.
Who am I gonna have to keep me company?
You still have Aunt Mam.
That’s different. She can’t replace you.
It’s nothing personal, Mam.
Yes.
If you feel lonely, why don’t you find something to do?
I’m sure you have many things you want to do,
especially meddling in Chan’s life.
How could I meddle in her life?
Mom.
While I’m away, can you please be nice to Chan?
I’m asking you.
Please.
I’ve got to leave now, otherwise I will miss my flight.
I’ll see you.
Have a safe flight.
Yes.
I won’t see you off.
I’m leaving.
Aunt Mam, please take care of my mom.
Why do you want me to come with you?
It’s so early.
I want you to come with me.
While waiting for you, I don’t know what to do.
I have plenty of time before my band practice at 1 p.m.
Just do what you always do when you come to my office.
You mean, sitting around?
You stare at me.
Oh.
Did you know that I was staring at you?
It would be weird if I didn’t know.
You couldn’t stop staring at me.
We've always stuck together lately.
Then you two should spend some time apart.
Mom.
Good morning, Madam.
Chan, you know what you need to do, right?
There’s nothing I need to worry about, right?
Yes.
Don’t worry, Mom.
I’m sorry for my mom.
It’s okay.
I shouldn’t have told you to come with me.
You asked me to come with you because you were worried about me.
I know that.
About your mom,
she is the real last boss, like Sun said.
But I believe that you can win her over.
Let’s go.
I thought
you weren’t this kind of person.
Do you have something to say to me?
You’re not someone who gives up easily.
The girl who is standing in front of me
is not Jay that I knew.
You are not fighting alone.
We have the same enemy.
So Jay,
don’t give up yet.
Simba.
Mommy and Mama are back.
Are you going to sleep over here?
Your sister went abroad for work.
I feel lonely.
So I want to spend time with you.
How long are you going to stay?
Indefinitely.
Whose cat is this?
That’s my cat, Mom.
I never permitted you to call me Mom.
I call you Mom
because you are Chan’s Mom.
I want to show you respect.
You are good at talking back.
Mom.
If you are going to stay with me, please don’t pick a fight.
Why?
Are you going to tell me to leave again?
I’ll call you Madam.
I’ll wait until you are comfortable letting me call you Mom.
It’s unlikely to happen.
Put the cat somewhere else.
I’m allergic to cats.
You’ve never had an allergy.
Yes, I do.
I’m allergic to all kinds of animal fur.
I got it.
I’ll keep Simba in the bedroom only.
Simba.
Let's go.
I told you to take the cat somewhere else,
not to keep it in your bedroom.
Where do you want me to take him?
Anywhere but here.
I told you I’m allergic to animal fur.
I’m keeping him only in my room.
That’s not enough.
Mom.
Don’t you feel bad for him?
Fine.
Don’t let it come near me.
I don’t want to see it.
Good night, Mom.
Good night.
Chan.
I’m not feeling well.
I think I’m going to be sick.
You are sick?
I’ll call Aunt Mam to come and take care of you.
No, it will take too long.
I want someone to take care of me right now.
Mom, I have to go to work.
I know that.
But she doesn’t have to go with you.
You want me to stay and take care of you?
If you have nothing else to do.
I only have a schedule this evening.
I have to perform with my band.
Okay.
I’ll have Eggs Benedict, avocado salad,
Kyoho grapes, and mineral water for breakfast.
For lunch, I want to eat Spanish food.
Do you know how to make paella?
Mom.
You can order it from a restaurant.
Why?
Can’t you prepare them for me?
Of course, I can.
No problem.
Mom.
Oops, I mean, Madam.
I don’t want to leave you alone with Mom.
It’s okay.
Don’t worry about me.
I think my mom must be up to something.
I know.
I also have something up my sleeve.
What is it?
I can’t tell you.
Will you two end up fighting again?
I think I should take leave today.
Don’t do that.
Even if you took leave, your mom wouldn’t leave me alone.
It would give her a chance to criticize you.
I’m worried about you.
You should go to work.
Fine.
Bye.
What’s up, Phu?
Every time you have that look on your face when you come to see me,
it’s always about Jay.
You’re right.
I told you.
If it’s about Jay, I don’t want to hear it.
Can you hear me out this time?
I won’t bother you about this again.
I came to tell you about Jay
because I feel bad for her.
I’ve never seen her in such a wreck.
She is a complete mess.
I think,
for the sake of our long friendship,
can you go talk to her?
So you won’t have anything unresolved between you two.
Jay wants to talk to you one last time.
I’m glad that you came to see me.
Phu told me you wanted to talk to me.
What is it?
If…
I hadn’t left you back then,
what do you think we’d be like now?
Would we still love each other?
Would we get married and have our happy ending?
Please say something.
Our relationship,
it’s too late.
The thing that you said,
it will never happen.
You and I,
we are not in love anymore.
Everything about us is just the past.
I want you to move on.
You need to focus on the present.
But I want to have you in my present.
No, Jay.
You and I can only be friends.
But I don’t want to be your friend.
This is the last time that we talk.
You know what?
I never thought I could be such a loser.
Then go back to being the old you.
Can you give me another chance?
You’re asking for something I can’t give you.
I really love Key.
Are you sure?
Jay.
I think our love is better left as a memory.
I want you…
to remember only the good memories about us.
Even though our love has ended,
I don’t want it to be ruined.
I can put myself back together.
So can you.
Jay that I knew, she can definitely do it.
Be careful.
Your mom…
will never accept Key.
Thank you.
Why did you stop walking?
Did I forget something?
Forgot what?
I’m asking you.
Did you forget your bag?
Where did you leave it?
Where do you think I left it?
In the car?
Then go check it.
I’ll put these bags in the room first. Then I’ll go down to check it.
No.
You need to go check it right now.
Can you take these bags to the room?
No.
I’m tired. I’ll go wait in the room.
Why don’t you take these bags with you?
I’ll go check your bag in the car.
Please.
No.
Why did it take you so long?
I almost don’t want to wait anymore.
I’m sorry to keep you waiting.
It looks similar to the original recipe.
Yes.
I cooked it for my family before.
Really?
Did they eat it?
They said it was delicious.
I learned it from a talented chef.
Did you hire a chef from Spain to teach you?
No.
I learned from Chef Niam,
a house helper who works for my family.
She is an amazing cook.
She learned the recipe from YouTube.
If it doesn’t taste good, I won’t eat it.
Yes, me too.
How is it?
Does it suit your palate, Mom?
I mean, Madam.
May I be excused to check on Simba?
What are you doing?
Why don’t you read my message?
What are they doing?
Mom, you seem to enjoy your meal.
Where is Key?
You smell so good.
(What are you doing, hooman?)
Key.
I’m watching our cat.
Meow.
Meow, meow.
(Do your best at work, hooman.)
This cat is quite something.
(Good luck with work.)
(Meow.)
Shit.
Again?
Yes.
You got drunk again.
You are wearing my pajamas.
Please wash before returning.
What happened last night?
Do you really want to know?
Don’t you remember…
what we did?
Elle.
Hi, Phu.
Did you follow me?
Calm down, Jay.
I invited her.
Why didn’t you tell me sooner?
So I would go to another bar.
Wait.
Why do you keep running away from me?
No, I don’t.
Are you…
having feelings for me?
No way.
Then let’s have a drink together.
Are you asking me out on a date?
Yes.
It’s a friend date.
Nothing romantic.
Nothing…
sexual.
Can I have a strong Vodka?
Do you dare?
I thought you would dare.
You live up to your reputation, Miss Boozer.
Can I have another glass?
I don’t get it.
What is so special about that girl?
Why is Chan so devoted to her?
It’s no longer your business.
Why are you worried about Chan?
How can I not be worried about her?
Look at what she’s doing.
But she doesn’t want you to fuss over her.
What Chat does is no longer your business.
The only thing that you can do right now…
is have a drink.
I secretly did some digging on you.
You are a well-known pilot.
You are the most talented female pilot in your class.
You like secretly dating flight attendants.
Who knows how many airlines you’ve dated by now?
I’m not a flight attendant.
But are you interested in keeping me company tonight?
So you and I,
did we sleep together?
No way.
Why don’t I remember anything?
I remember that we were in a nightclub.
Then I blacked out.
Why are you laughing?
Listen.
Since the day you first met me,
the closest that we got was
when you rolled over to hold me before you woke up.
Nothing happened between us.
Because I rejected you.
After that, you got wasted
and threw up on the side of the road again.
So I needed to take you back to my room.
I changed your clothes.
Then I put you into the bed because I felt sorry for you.
Do you get it now?
That’s not true.
Sorry, but it’s true, darling.
You should go take a shower. Then I’ll give you a ride home.
Why will you give me a ride home?
When you get drunk next time,
I’ll know where to drop you off.
So you won’t have to sleep over here, honey.
Or do you want me to help you take a shower?
Come here.
-You weren’t resisting last night. -No.
Aren’t you going to say thank you?
Thank you for giving me a ride.
Do you want to get a cup of coffee tomorrow?
Are you asking me out on a date?
It’s just friends hanging out.
No?
Are you having feelings for me?
Is that a joke?
I have no feelings for you.
So?
Are you going?
If you say no, I’ll go ask someone else.
My answer is no.
Do whatever you want.
Okay. I got it.
Have a nice day, Miss Jay.
That’s it? Aren’t you going to try a little harder?
What the f*ck!
Don’t drag this out.
You’ll only end up hurting more.
I agree.
You should come to terms with Chan’s decision.
No matter what, I will never break up with Chan.
Can I ask you something?
Do you really think Chan will choose you over me?
She doesn’t need to choose.
She can have us both.
Is that so?
We are only going to take our hatred out on each other.
It will be very toxic.
Don’t you feel sorry for Chan?
Why do we have to hate each other?
No way.
Mom.
I love you.
I invited you to join me today.
Because I want you to be present
in the most important moment of my life.
I will use these earrings
to propose to you.
Will you marry me, Key?
Your mom will never accept me.
Don’t give up yet.
Don’t leave me.
I will never give up on us.
I want you to stop holding on to it.
If you keep doing this,
you may end up losing Chan as a friend.
Simba.
I don’t know where Mom took Simba.
I checked the camera. I didn’t see anyone home.
I’m afraid that Mom is willing to do anything to win.
Honey.
What do you want to talk to me about?
Key is the only one I will marry.
If you want me to accept your marriage,
then you need to give me something in exchange.